# TINTU CHACKO

28B Freyberg Street, Waterloo, Lower Hutt, 5011.

Mobile: 02102745782

Email: tintuchacko2012@gmail.com **VISA STATUS – RESIDENT VISA** 

GitHub: https://github.com/tintuchacko LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/t1991/

## **OBJECTIVE**

To build a career in a leading corporate Hi-Tech environment with committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore my abilities fully and realize my potential. Willing to work as a key player in a challenging and creative environment.

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake, or situation that I am presented with. As a postgraduate with two years of experience in PHP programming, I am excellent at working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence. I consider myself to be hardworking and enjoy learning.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Web Designing and PHP, HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Programming

SQL, iQuery, AJAX, C, C++, JAVA, WAMP, XAMPP,

MVC, OOPs.

Database MySQL, SQL Server.

Operating system MS Windows 2000/XP/Windows 7/Windows8/Windows

10, Linux

Framework Codeigniter

**Tools** GitHub, Sublime Text, Visual studio Code, Eclipse,

Brackets, JS Fiddle, Dreamweaver, Microsoft Office

suite(Word, Excel, PowerPoint).

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

- Positive attitude.
- Work well in a team.
- Conscientious and determined to achieve goals.
- Responsible.
- Quick learner.
- Can research and work independently.

## **WORK HISTORY**

## **Oges Infotech**

Kerala, India June 2015 - Sep 2017

# **PHP Programmer**

Database Designing, developing, perform integration tests, client deployment, collect and make changes according to client feedback, etc.

## **Technolodge**

Kerala, India Dec 2014 - May 2015

## PHP Developer (Codeigniter) Trainee

Training for Database Designing, Website Designing, developing in Codeigniter framework, testing.

## **QUALIFICATIONS**

Mar Athanasius College

Kerala, India 2011 - 2014

Mar Athanasius College

Kerala, India 2011 - 2012

Indira Gandhi College of Arts and Science

Kerala, India 2008 - 2011

**Master of Computer Applications (MCA)** 

**Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Application (PGDCA)** 

**BSc. Computer Science** 

#### REFERENCES

**Jithin Jose** 

**Project Manager OGES INFOTECH** +91 9061672364 jithin@ogesinfotech.com Harikrishnan C Nair

Team Leader **OGES INFOTECH** +91 9633739303 hari@ogesinfotech.com